http://www.loucoll.ac.uk/documents-and-policies

Assets
gold-crest-gradient Created with Sketch.
Home
XInternational Students Looking for our International Website? Click on the link below to go there.International Website
Quick LinksFind A CourseGet an ApprenticeshipCareer IdeasGet in touch
A
Accounts 2014-2015 Loughborough College Accounts 2015-2016 Loughborough College Accounts 2016-2017 Loughborough College Accounts 2017-2018 Loughborough College Accounts 2018-2019 Loughborough College Accounts 2018-2019 The Leicestershire CollegeAppeals Process - AdmissionsAppeals Form - AdmissionsAppeals Process - Exam Results (Summer 2020)Appeals Form - Exam ResultsAnti Bullying Policy Attendance and Punctuality Procedure
B
Brand Guidelines - June 2019
C
College Values Complaints ProcedureCriminal Convictions Policy
E
English and Mathematics Skills Policy
Examination Access Arrangements Policy
F
Fee Policy 2020/21 Financial Regulations
G
GDPR Readiness Statement Template Gender Pay Report - 2019
H
Health and Safety Policy - Loughborough College Health and Safety Policy - The Leicestershire College Higher Education Arrangements for students to transfer Higher Education Access and Participation Plan 2019-20 Higher Education Access Agreement 2018-19 Higher Education Admissions Policy Higher Education Access Agreement 2017-18 Higher Education Access Agreement 2016-17 Higher Education Access Agreement 2015-16 Higher Education Academic Misconduct Policy Higher Education Appeals Policy Higher Education College Examination Regulations for Loughborough University validated Higher Education Enrolment and Withdrawal Policy Higher Education Ethics Policy Higher Education Extenuating Circumstances Higher Education Support, Policy and Procedure Higher Education Learner Agreement and College Code Higher Education Student Protection Plan Higher Education The Student Contract
L
Learner Disciplinary Policy and Procedure Learner Recruitment Policy Learning Support Policy Loughborough College 16-19 Small Group Tuition FundLoughborough College Strategy 2025 - Shaping Futures
O
OFS Transparency Return 2018-19
P
Prevent PolicyPrivacy Policy Privacy Notice - StudentsPrivacy Notice - NurseryPrivacy Notice - Workforce
S
Safeguarding Policy Safeguarding Policy - Annex Subcontracted Provision Statement Subcontracting fees and charges policy 2020-21
T
Trade Union Facility Time - 2019
W
Whistle Blowing Policy
AboutCollegeApplyNow
QuickEnquiry
Open Days - Register your interest
We will let you know when future dates become availableRegister
Loughborough College
AccommodationAdult Funding GuideApplication ProcessAbout CollegeVirtual TourHow to find usFinancial SupportLoughborough Students UnionSomething to Say?Student SupportUndergraduate policies and documents
Why Loughborough?
Loughborough Students UnionVoted No. 1 for student experience, LSU offers hundreds of opportunities for you to get involved and get activeFind out more
Menu
Courses
College Information About the CollegeVirtual TourHow to Get HereTerm DatesAccommodationDownload ProspectusOrder a ProspectusSomething to Say? AccessibilityParentsDocuments and PoliciesPublication SchemeAccreditationsGoverning BodyJob VacanciesOfS Transparency ReturnAccessibility Statement
Students & Staff
Student Support Student Links Staff Dashboard Report Absence
Radmoor Centre
Hair, Beauty and Spa Radmoor Restaurant Sport & Leisure
Other Sites
International Students Employers & Business Library Radmoor Nursery School Sport Apprenticeships
JOB VACANCIESCORONAVIRUS (COVID-19) Advice & UpdatesSummer 2020 Results InformationUse of this website constitutes acceptance of Loughborough College’s Privacy Policy including cookie-use.
